(Leonard:)Sheldon, you do this all the time.
(Leonard:)You fixate on some crazy idea
and then blow it way out of proportion.
(Sheldon:)Name one time I've ever done that.
(Leonard:)How about when you put GPS trackers
in your garbage...
(Leonard:)...because you were convinced North
Korean spies were stealing your doodles.
(Leonard:)The chicken nuggets
you were sure were human nuggets.
(Leonard:)The strangely-shaped cloud
that was following you around town.
(Leonard:)The time you put on my shirt...
(Leonard:)...and were convinced
you'd started growing again.
(Sheldon:)I said name one. You really need
to work on your listening skills.
Penny. Penny. Penny.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)You need to remove that chair
from the building. It's a heaIth hazard.
(Penny:)I took off the slipcovers, had them
dry-cleaned and fumigated the cushions.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's cleaner than my couch.